question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 'Sonic Adventure', you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the 'Half-Life' series, 'H.E.V' stands for 'Hazardous Evasiveness Vest'",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The name of the attack 'Kamehameha' in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "'Santa Claus' is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
